<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>  on Step Up Tutors</title>
    <link>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in   on Step Up Tutors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>Step Up Tutors</copyright><atom:link href="https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Key Stage 2 SATs</title>
      <link>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/ks2-sats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/ks2-sats/</guid>
      <description>For children preparing for Key Stage 2 SATs, I can provide the next Step Up to ensure they are comfortable and ready. I have access to past papers and can:
 assess your child’s strengths and weaknesses in relation to the tests and use this information to target the support I give; take your child through reading and maths questions; sharpen up their writing style across the full range of text types; give guidance on test technique; prepare pupils for the Spelling, Grammar and Punctuation Test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specific Learning Difficulties</title>
      <link>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/specific-learning-difficulties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/specific-learning-difficulties/</guid>
      <description>I have a diploma in dyslexia and am experienced in teaching children with specific learning difficulties such as dyslexia, dyspraxia and dyscalculia. I teach through a multisensory approach, combining visual, auditory and kinaesthetic learning.
I am knowledgeable in teaching phonics to aid reading and spelling. I have lots of engaging activities and multisensory approaches that I use. I make sure that the programme I devise for each child is highly structured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Approaches</title>
      <link>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/teaching-approaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/teaching-approaches/</guid>
      <description>Many children struggle with maths and reading. I use various practical resources to help them form mental pictures. These pictures are the building-blocks of understanding that will last your child a lifetime.
Some children require lots of practice and reinforcement. I provide this in varied ways to keep their interest and attention.
When designing teaching programmes, I ensure there are lots of visual, auditory and kinaesthetic activities to strengthen learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your First Session</title>
      <link>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/your-first-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuck1s.github.io/stepuptutors-co-uk/your-first-session/</guid>
      <description>We’ll chat things through, to make sure I understand exactly what you want, and what your child needs. I will carefully assess your child’s strengths, and also identify areas where they need support and extension. Then I create a tailored teaching programme for your child and will review this with you, and answer any questions you may have.
  As your child learns and develops, I adjust and reshape the programme to ensure they continue to progress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
